Huh?
Wait, what's going on here?
If anything comes up, I'll drop it
in the group chat we just made.
Who could've seen
this coming?
Life is strange,
and I feel alive
Okay, see you.
Mizuhara... Mizuhara!
I'll get going, too.
Cruel world!!
dun
Wait, who is this?
His name means
"Sword of truth" in Malay
I'm letting him stay in your room.
Don't assume you'll
have your grandmother
and your room forever
Wait, my room?!
You're not
using it
I'll look for a new place
Everything's destroying my mental state.
while I eat...
I thought I was good at going it alone
Would you prefer to go together?
Place
your finger here
Rent-a-Girlfriend
"Moving and Girlfriend"
Hey, Kazuya.
Kazuya!
Wake up already!
The members of the shopping arcade
association are coming over today.
And why aren't you at school?
Are you trying to turn the living
room into your bedroom?
voom
But most of all,
what's with all the snack bags?
It shows
your character
Did you go to sleep without brushing?!
Ow! Sorry! I said I'm sorry!
Good morning.
Right, you have
a PM shift
Hello there, Saifur.
Wha?!
Heh, guess I have no place here anymore.
This ain't too bad
Savings Account
Credit (Yen)                             Debit (Yen)                                      Balance (Yen)
I have 5,400 yen in my account.
Sigh...
Sighs of the nation
This is just
pocket change
I had no idea
I was in such
a bad way...!!
Poverty...!!
Sure, payday's coming up, but that's
no number for an account balance.
I don't regret the money
I spent on Mizuhara.
I did end up having huge
unforeseen expenses, too.
This is no time
to be depressed!!
I need to find a new place
This is what I get for skipping work
so many times at the start of the year!
I can't do anything
with this paltry capital!
I can't waste a single yen
with the apartment visits.
The new place can't be
any more expensive, either.
RealEstateSearch.com
Search
Max Rent
Min Rent
Moving season just ended, so there
won't be many places available.
And if it's not a walkable distance from
school, I'll just spend more money.
35,000 yen...
Found 1 result
Ack, just one result?
Available from May 19
And I can't move in
until a month from now?
Cries of
the nation
I'm screwed.
Rent in Tokyo is way too high!
I had to look for ages
before finding Royal Hills, too.
A super
cheap apartment...
She's way too frugal
It was a miracle that a girl like
Mizuhara was living in that dump.
Wonder what she's doing right now.
She said she was going home.
Won't she feel lonely all by herself?
She's currently investigating,
so maybe I can suggest we be roommates.
Wait, what am I thinking?
There're all sorts
of issues with that!!
You and your delusions!!
That's living together!
She'd never move in with
a guy she's not even dating!
And she doesn't seem anywhere
near ready to start dating me.
So what is she thinking?
She's not getting in touch with me.
She's gonna carry on with her life,
and she'll keep meeting other guys.
Not to doubt her
or anything
We might just end up drifting apart.
Ugh
Not again!
She has nothing to worry
about in that regard.
She's only looking into
her own feelings, anyway.
And if my feelings change,
she'll just move on.
We're too far apart!!
I love her
even if she doesn't
feel the same way!!
That sounds like she
doesn't like me at all!
Damn it! This is the problem
with super-popular girls!
The moment you fall in love,
you're fighting a losing battle.
And the only weapon you have is passion.
There's nothing I can do
but keep giving her my love.
Wait, guys have, like, no power here.
What ever happened to gender equality?
Hello, Chizuru-chan.
Long time no see.
Hello.
You're looking more and more
like your mother.
You think so?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Miso soup
with tofu
Rice
Mackerel w/ miso
Beans
(5 types)
Orange
Broccoli
Tomato
Time to eat.
So, you got some high scores.
How do you two feel about that?
It's all down to me.
I wrote the material, too,
so this is my personal score.
Yeah, right.
Wait, are you serious?
I was there with you!
You all saw me there, right?
What's wrong? Do you have a cold?
I'm fine. You worry too much.
Kawanaki Hiroki
Kinoshita Kazuya
Kelly
Director Koga
I should do the dishes.
South Narimasu Arcade
What's up, Yaemori-san?
Why'd you ask me to come out?
Why at this hour?
I figured we could chat if you were
feeling awkward in your family home.
Bingo
You're totally... not wrong.
You can come over (for 2 mins)
Kibe and Kuribayashi were heartless,
so I'm grateful for the invite.
I hate guys, actually
You know what I think?
I think you and Mizuhara-san
need to live together!
Huh?
What do you mean?
What is she even saying?
I mean, I would if I could.
But why suddenly bring this up?
Does she have a plan?
Anyway, let's go drink!
No plan
Nope! No plan!
It all starts with a
brainstorming session!
Getting chased out
of your apartment
is a living together setup
I realized that while
watching a rom-com
As your official main supporter,
Love will save the world!
I can't let you two be!
Since when?
Also, what's with the cat ears?
Oh, I just forgot to take 'em off.
Why'd you even have them on?
She's not a bad kid, really.
You said you were going over
For better or for worse,
they're blah about everything
Your friends are okay
with you stepping out?
Totally. I told 'em I had
important matters to take care of.
Well, I felt weird being home,
and this will help get my mind off things.
Like, aren't you lonely,
being separated from Mizuhara-san?!
Aren't you being assailed
by infinite sadness?!
No! Nothing like that!
Blegh
hic
Mizuhara!
Cry all you want tonight.
Sorry! I'm so sorry!
You really went to town
No prob. It's good to know
that you're actually hurting.
I have no idea what she's thinking!
I mean, we lived in that building
for two whole years!
Even if she feels nothing for me,
does she have no attachment to the place?
Yeah... but she did say
she'd look into it.
I find it hard to believe she
won't miss you at all, either.
Yeah! That's exactly it!
What is she,
an android?!
That means she has some
positive feelings for me!
But did you see her face? Zero emotion!
Wonder where her family home is.
Around a ten-minute walk from the station?
Wait, why do you know this?!
Oops
That's amazing progress!!
You went there?! You need
to share this stuff with me!
I was going to tell you, okay?
I slipped up...
She was planning to put it up for sale.
I just went to help clean it up.
It was nothing special.
I was just
manual labor
What are you saying?!
You think she'd invite a guy she feels
nothing for over to her family home?!
Truth nuke...
But now I'm actually worried.
Huh?
This investigation's
actually a risky gamble.
The fact that she's developed feelings
and still doesn't have an answer
could mean she doesn't intend
to give you one at all.
I mean, she could've done this
while you were dating.
Concerning
This is basically a waste of your time.
Any other guy would take
the hint and walk away.
I'm not doubting Mizuhara-san here,
but in general,
girls like that are bad news.
I'll give it a real shot.
No way.
Huh?
I'm grateful you're taking my side,
but I believe in Mizuhara.
With all my heart.
You're so in love, it's almost laughable.
That's what's so great about you, though.
Well, I'm not laughing.
I was just speaking
in general terms
But I believe in Mizuhara-san, too.
I'm still cheering you two on,
no matter what.
Wait, what?
I just sent a pic of you to our
three-person group chat.
Royal Hills Refugees (3)
Yaemori Mini
Huh?!
What?! What's wrong with you?!
clatter
Who said
you could?!
I bet Mizuhara-san's
lonely all by herself, too.
Are you outta your mind?
Are you really trying
to help with this pic?!
If you had to
Send something better!
That beauty's getting
too comfortable
It's fine.
You need to light a fire under her ass
by showing you're alone with a girl.
You know that's not gonna work.
Not Mizuhara
of all people...
Ichinose Chizuru
Someone's having fun
See? Just look at this!
Just text
"Someone's having fun," she says.
Are you kidding me?!
Ichinose Chizuru
Someone's having fun
Wouldn't you normally use an emoji there?
Is she made of metal?!
She's not lonely
at all!!
Feels like she
messed up again
Good thing she
replied, huh!!
Her heart hasn't budged an inch!
She doesn't care about me at all!
Hey, but you are having fun, aren't you?
She just said
what she thought
That's not helping!
I'm doomed. She must
be with some other guy.
She's just like, "We're kissing
right now. Stop bothering us."
Huh?
What now...
Ichinose Chizuru
Mind if I join you?
What?!
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Is this the place?
Go to Bed
Delete event
This event has been deleted
One new customer,
meeting her friends
Welcome!
Oh, damn.
What do we have here?
Whoa, that's one fine girl.
Is she alone?
She's meeting friends, apparently.
Are you serious?
Way to take my breath away.
A girl that hot in this part of town?
Look at that rack!
Man, I wish I could drink
with a girl like her.
Are they filming something here?
But she's by herself.
She's not above a cheap izakaya, huh?
Check out the contrast with
the office workers behind her.
I wish she'd join us by mistake.
Her legs are so fair.
Where were we, again?
I forgot.
Hey, Chizuru-san. Over here.
She must be
an idol?
What, just a regular group
of college students?
That guy doesn't look like
her boyfriend. Good.
Buzz off
Hello.
The staff can't pick up your
empty glasses fast enough.
I only had one drink.
Come on, take a seat
It was all Master.
Looking real pretty again.
Hey, it's our job.
The drink's not
going anywhere
She's here!
Mizuhara really showed up
at this cheap izakaya!
You've got a silver tongue.
I wasn't trying to flatter you.
You're in a league of your own.
"Mind if I join you?"
Why? For what purpose?
Ichinose Chizuru
Someone's having fun
Mind if I join you?
Was Yaemori-san right? Was she lonely?
Her texts were so curt,
I couldn't tell how she was feeling.
But maybe she really did miss me?
And Yaemori-san
Still, Mizuhara...
How'd she pull off that look
when this was all unplanned?
It can't just be the booze telling
me she's a perfect ten again!
Most places like this use
tablets for ordering these days.
She's so heavenly,
she's even raising the pub's value!
What will you have?
Well, I already ate.
The makeup's giving her a sense
of natural precious metal!
Drinks only, then?
That thin spring blouse can't conceal
the explosive aura of her body!
Her collar covers her neck and shows
that she's got her guard up.
And her long legs show off
her fair skin and slender build.
Skort
And is that a skirt or shorts?
The mystery has all men on edge!
Every man in this place is more
fixated on her than on their booze!
One day away and
I can't handle
her hotness!!
Don't let it go to your head, me!
This ultimate Venus couldn't
possibly be missing a guy like me!
Hey.
You're drinking too much.
Drunkard!
Hey, I have tomorrow off.
Here you go.
Your pay. Before I forget.
I said it's fine.
And I said it's not.
Nothing more expensive than free.
The sale's on hold,
and I couldn't ask you to help
put things back if I didn't pay.
Okay, so she came to give me this.
Yeah, she's so unemotional about things.
Okay, see you.
Makes sense, given how she was acting.
There's no way she was just lonely.
I guess I should be happy she's
willing to ask for my help again.
What can I get for you?
Oh...
I'll have a highball.
Wait, you're drinking?
She's drinking? So she didn't
come just to give me my pay?
People only order highballs
when they're in
the mood to get drunk...
She was lonely? There's still
a chance she missed me?
Am I allowed to interpret this as
her being here to drink with me?
Highball? Nice
Can you hold your liquor?
Well, I'm not a lightweight, at least.
Not that I can tell myself.
Heck,
it's always me...
Yeah, I've never seen her plastered.
But I mean, as a rental girlfriend,
you must've drunk
with clients lots of times.
Look at her go
Like it's no biggie
Yaemori-san showed
no hesitation in asking!
You sure that's okay to ask?
Would she answer that?!
I'm focusing while I'm at work,
so I don't get drunk or anything.
Is it okay tonight?!
Here you are.
Thank you.
Let's just say anything goes tonight.
Anything goes? Really?!
Let us three Royal Hills refugees
drink and lick our wounds!
There, there. It must've hurt, uwu!
Now cheers!
To reality attacking
on us like titans
bwahaha
yay yay
Let's break up.
Wait, why?
Because you've been staring at that girl
over there the whole time, that's why!
N-No, Yumi!
Man, it's hot.
I think I worked up a sweat.
Mizuhara's going quite hard.
Do you want a refill, Mizuhara-san?
She's guzzling down those drinks.
She's really letting go...
or letting it all out, even.
What a view!!
It's starting to feel like she's giving me
the green light to ask her things.
Looked like you
drank quite a bit
before I showed up
So, what were you two talking about?
Oh, we were talking about you, obviously.
Master has nothing to
talk about except you
Wha?!
Hey, now you're making me curious.
Yaemori-san!
Just go ahead and give it to her.
Anything goes tonight, and it's
better to share how you're feeling.
This "anything
goes" thing
is just you
saying things
Don't just toss me a live grenade!
He said something
about me, huh?
If you've got something
to say, spit it out.
I never said it was taboo, and besides,
I don't like feeling like
you're tiptoeing around me.
Easy for her to say!
Like it's no big deal at all!
Yeah, I've got lots of stuff I wanna say!
Like, "What made you come here tonight,"
"What were you up to yesterday,"
or "How do you feel about me?"
I said I'd wait,
but I'm honestly worried sick.
Because we've been split apart
and won't meet as often anymore.
I-It's nothing special.
But you said you'd "look into it,"
so why does it feel like getting
kicked out doesn't bother you at all?
D-Don't you feel the least bit sad?
Watching-the-Show Form
Welp, I went and said it.
There's no way she does.
This is just me blurting
out that I miss her.
We're talking about the
one-percenter Mizuhara here.
There's no way she'd ever miss me.
I do.
I do!
And?
That was a pretty big quake yesterday.
Maybe I should do something to
make sure these don't fall over.
That's the umeshu Chizuru-san
gave me on my birthday.
Did you hear that, Master?!
I-I did, but settle down.
Mizuhara-san said,
"I wish my collegemate and neighbor in
room 203 would hug me on lonely nights."
That's what she said!
I said no such thing!
Now's your chance!
Let's go with Operation Go For It!
W-W-Wait! I'm not ready for this!
Ugh, enough of that.
Next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Loneliness and...
...Girlfriend."
Don't wimp out, Master!
This is why you're a vir—
I-I can't wait for the next episode!
"Loneliness and Girlfriend"